

CONTACT



9923988650



prashantp5sharma.1998@gmail.com



H.No. 27-B, Air Force Station, Mullanpur Garibdass, Mohali, Punjab, 140901 INDIA

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS
- Redux Toolkit

LINKS

Portfolio: https://prashant-sharma.netlify.app/

GitHub: https://github.com/wolf-dagger

LANGUAGE

- ENGLISH
- HINDI

PRASHANT SHARMA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

As a forward-thinking Software Engineer with a keen eye for innovation, I bring a wealth of experience in leading high-energy teams and delivering exceptional results. Now, I am poised to pivot my skills towards the fast-paced world of web development, with a particular focus on mastering React.js.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER, MPHASIS Pvt. Ltd.
JUNE 2021-JULY 2022

I worked as an Associate Software Engineer on PeopleSoft Technology, building, processing, and handling them in the deployment phase. I also worked on MySQL and managed the Tables in the database. I also worked on GitHub.

React Js Intern, Omninos Software Solutions Pvt. Ltd. Oct 2022 – April 2023

Worked as an Intern on React Js Technology where I learned to make websites with re-usable components. Also worked on different problems and solved them. Also, possess a good understanding of GIT Hub. Worked on live projects too. Also did some projects on a personal level

EDUCATION

B.E./B.Tech., CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY, Mohali

JUNE2017 — MAY2021

Stream: Computer Science Engineering

Specialization: Internet Of Things

CGPA: 7.07

PROJECTS

Portfolio: https://prashant-sharma.netlify.app/

Cart System: https://amazoon-cart-system-prashant.netlify.app/

ToDo App: https://amazoon-cart-system-prashant.netlify.app/

CRUD APP: https://prashant-crud-app.netlify.app/

Weather App: https://wolf-dagger.github.io/weatherApp